Finding Aid for Gerald L. K. Smith Papers 1922-1976
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Chronological files
  - Radio speeches 1932, 1938-1942
    - Speech memos
      - 1940 (Box 6)
      - 1941 (Box 6)
    - Speech notices (Box 6)
    - Springer, Harvey H. (Box 7)
    - Squire, Burt (Box 7)
    - Stadsklev, C. O. (Box 7)
      (Truth and Liberty Radio)
    - Stanley, Mrs. David (Box 7)
      (United Mothers of Michigan)
    - Stewart, Charles H. (Box 7)
    - Stutz, David (Box 7)
    - Sutter, Katherine M. (Box 7)
    - T (miscellaneous) (Box 7)
    - U (miscellaneous) (Box 7)
    - V (miscellaneous) (Box 7)
    - Vandenberg, Arthur H. (Box 7)
    - W (miscellaneous) (Box 7)
    - WJR (Box 7)
      (Detroit radio station)
    - WOL (Box 7)
      (Washington radio station; speeches and correspondence)
    - Welch, James (Box 7)
    - Winrod, Gerald (Box 7)
      (see also Defender)
    - Woodruff, Roy O. (Box 7)
    - Y-Z (miscellaneous) (Box 7)
  - 1943
    - A (miscellaneous) (Box 7)
    - America First miscellanea (Box 7)
    - American Council of Christian Churches (Box 7)
    - American Legion (Box 7)
    - Anti-Defamation League (Box 7)
    - Asman, Lorence (Box 7)
    - B (miscellaneous) (Box 7)
    - Banta, Edwin P. (Box 7)
    - Buffalo Meeting (Box 7)
    - Buffalo Courier Express (Box 7)
      (re Smith letter, June 1, 1943)
    - Buroker, L. Peres (Box 7)
    - C (miscellaneous) (Box 7)
    - Carlson [John Roy] (Box 7)
      (flyer)
    - Chicago Meeting (Box 7)
    - Christmas Cards (Box 7)
    - Cleveland Rally (Box 7)
      (Special Flag Day Rally)
    - Cleveland Rally (Box 7)
      (American First Party)
    - Committee for Constitutional Government (Box 7)
    - Confidential Memos (Box 7)
    - Connally Resolution (Box 7)
    - Cooper, Ida (Box 7)
    - Corey, George H. (Box 7)
    - Cross and the Flag: background papers
      - February 1943 (Box 7)
      - May 1943 (Box 8)
      - June 1943 (Box 8)
      - July 1943 (Box 8)
      - August 1943 (Box 8)
      - September 1943, 2 folders (Box 8)
      - October 1943, 2 folders (Box 8)
      - November 1943 (Box 8)
      - December 1943 (Box 8)
      - Miscellaneous 1943 (Box 8)
    - Crusading Mothers of Pennsylvania (Box 8)
    - D (miscellaneous) (Box 8)
    - Dayton Rally (Box 8)
    - Debate with Preston Slosson (Box 8)
    - Denver meeting (Box 8)
    - Detroit meeting (Box 8)
    - Dies Committee (Box 8)
    - Dilling, Elizabeth (Box 8)
    - E (miscellaneous) (Box 8)
    - Erie Rally (Box 8)
    - F (miscellaneous) (Box 8)
    - Federal Bureau of Investigation (Box 8)
    - Federation of Americanization of Michigan, Inc. (Box 8)
    - Forrer, Samuel H. (Box 8)
    - Friends of the Constitution (Box 8)
    - G (miscellaneous) (Box 8)
    - Goff, Kenneth O. (Box 8)
    - H (miscellaneous) (Box 8)
    - Harsh, C. M. (Box 8)
    - Hart, Merwin K. (Box 8)
      (National Economic Council)
    - Haushalter, Walter (Box 8)
    - Heggblom, U.S.A. (Box 8)
    - Herrstrom, W. D. (Box 8)
    - Hoffman, Clare E. (Box 9)
    - Hour (periodical) (Box 9)
    - Hughes, Langston (Box 9)
    - Hungry Club (Box 9)
      (Edward A. Tabor)
    - In Fact (periodical) (Box 9)
    - Internal Revenue Office (Box 9)
    - Issues (Box 9)
      (statement of issues to be used in 1944 election)
    - J (miscellaneous) (Box 9)
    - Jews: miscellaneous collected materials (Box 9)
    - Jones, J. Edward (Box 9)
    - K (miscellaneous) (Box 9)
    - Koch, William S. (Box 9)
    - L (miscellaneous) (Box 9)
    - Liebold, Ernest (Box 9)
      (Henry Ford secretary)
    - Lohle, Marie (Box 9)
    - Long, Earl (Box 9)
    - Los Angeles meeting (Box 9)
    - Louisiana politics: campaign materials (Box 9)
    - Lundeen, Mrs. Ernest (Box 9)
    - M (miscellaneous) (Box 9)
    - Mc (miscellaneous) (Box 9)
    - Mackinac Island Conference of Republican Leaders (Box 9)
    - Madden, Charles (Box 9)
      (Defenders of George Washington's Principles)
    - Maier, Walter (Box 9)
      (The Lutheran Hour)
    - Marion, L. L. (General) (Box 9)
    - Marion, L. L.
      (controversy over gas rationing)
      - Correspondence (Box 9)
      - Clippings (Box 9)
    - Maxon, Lou (Box 9)
      (Adcraft Club speech)
    - Meetings to be scheduled (Box 9)
    - Memos (miscellaneous) (Box 9)
    - Mencken, H. L. (Box 9)
    - Michigan Press Association: rate book and directory (Box 9)
    - Milwaukee Community Forum (Box 9)
    - Minneapolis meeting (Box 9)
    - Minnesota Bible College (Box 9)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 9)
    - Morrison, Mrs. Cressy (Box 9)
      (American Women Against Communism)
    - Mote, Carl H. (Box 9)
    - N (miscellaneous) (Box 9)
    - New Party (Box 9)
    - Newspaper clippings (Box 9)
    - Newspapers: lists (Box 9)
    - Nowak, Stanley (Box 9)
    - Nye, Gerald P. (Box 9)
    - Nye, Gerald P. (Box 9)
      (meeting in Detroit)
    - O (miscellaneous) (Box 9)
    - P (miscellaneous) (Box 9)
    - Parker, Frank (Box 10)
      (Green Mountaineer)
    - Phelps, G. Allison (Box 10)
    - Philadelphia meeting (Box 10)
    - Pittsburgh meetings (Box 10)
    - PM: Daily Newspaper (Box 10)
    - Prentice-Hall, Inc. (Box 10)
    - Press releases (Box 10)
    - R (miscellaneous) (Box 10)
    - Race riot - Detroit
      - Press releases, correspondence, etc. (Box 10)
      - Clippings (Box 10)
    - References (Box 10)
    - Republican Lecture Course (Box 10)
    - Reynolds, Robert R. (Box 10)
    - Romer, Harry (Box 10)
    - Rubber, synthetic (Box 10)
    - S (miscellaneous) (Box 10)
    - Saginaw Rally: America First Party (Box 10)
    - Salt Lake City meeting (Box 10)
    - San Francisco meeting (Box 10)
    - Slosson, Preston (see debate) (Box 10)
    - Smith, Dean E. (Box 10)
    - Smith, Gerry (Box 10)
    - Smith (personal (Box 10)
    - Smith (parents) (Box 10)
    - Smith family - personal (Box 10)
    - Smith biographical and testimonial material (Box 10)
    - Southard, Earl (Box 10)
    - Springer, Harvey H. (Box 10)
      (Western Voice)
    - Stadsklev, C. O. (Box 10)
    - Stanley, Mrs. David (Box 10)
      (United Mother's of America)
    - Stoffel, Joseph H. (Box 10)
      (The Economic League)
    - T (miscellaneous) (Box 10)
    - Telephone change (Box 10)
    - Threats (Box 10)
    - Toledo Rally: America First Party (Box 10)
    - Topeka meeting (Box 10)
    - Tucker, Ray (Box 10)
      (article in Columbus (Ohio) Journal)
    - U (miscellaneous) (Box 10)
    - "Undelivered Speech" (Box 10)
    - Undercover (Box 10)
      (book by John Roy Carlson, pseud.)
    - Union Now (Box 10)
    - V (miscellaneous) (Box 10)
    - Vandenberg, Arthur H. (Box 10)
    - W (miscellaneous) (Box 11)
    - Wheeler, Burton K. (Box 11)
    - Williams, Claude (Box 11)
    - Winchell, Walter (Box 11)
    - Winrod, Gerald P. (Box 11)
    - Woodruff, Roy O. (Box 11)
  - 1944
    - A (miscellaneous) (Box 11)
    - America First Party
      - Appeals and statements: mimeographed (Box 11)
      - Ballot Proofs (sample) (Box 11)
      - Minnesota (Box 11)
      - National Convention (Box 11)
      - National Convention (Box 11)
        (Platform Committee)
      - National Convention: Registration Forms, 2 folders (Box 11)
      - Nominations and miscellaneous items (Box 11)
      - Notices of meetings (Box 11)
      - Petitions (Box 11)
      - Principles (Box 11)
      - State campaign (Box 11)
      - State convention, July 31 (Box 11)
      - State convention, July 31 - registration forms (Box 11)
    - American Civil Liberties Union (Box 11)
    - American Council of Christian Churches (Box 11)
    - American Nationalists' Committee of Independent Voters (Box 11)
    - Anonymous (Box 11)
    - Arlt, Eric (Box 11)
    - Asman, Lorence (Box 11)
    - B (miscellaneous) (Box 11)
    - Baltimore meeting (Box 11)
    - Baerman, Ralph (Box 11)
    - Banta, Edwin P. (Box 11)
    - Board of Education (Detroit) (Box 11)
    - Bowles, Chester (Box 11)
      (gasoline rationing)
    - Bricker, (Gov.) John (Box 11)
    - Bricker, (Gov.) John (clippings) (Box 11)
    - Brown, Catharine V. (Box 11)
      (SEE National Blue Star Mothers of America)
    - Buffalo meeting (Box 12)
    - Buffalo (Box 12)
      (responses to free speech fund-raising appeal)
    - C (miscellaneous) (Box 12)
    - Campaign Expenditures Committee (Box 12)
    - Campaign clippings (Box 12)
    - Chicago meeting (Box 12)
    - Chicago Sun article on G.L.K. Smith (Box 12)
    - Cincinnati - prospective meeting (Box 12)
    - Circulars (Box 12)
    - Cleveland meetings (Box 12)
    - Close, Upton (Box 12)
    - Collier's (Box 12)
    - Correspondence (miscellaneous) (Box 12)
    - Cross and the Flag promotional letters (Box 12)
    - Cross and the Flag manuscripts? (Box 12)
    - D (miscellaneous) (Box 12)
    - Darke County (Ohio) Farmers' Controversy (clippings) (Box 12)
    - Daugherty, J. M. (Box 12)
    - Democratic National Convention (Box 12)
    - Detroit meetings (Box 12)
    - Dewey, Thomas (Box 12)
    - Dewey, Thomas, campaign clippings (Box 12)
    - Dies Committee clippings and printed matter (Box 12)
    - Dilling, Elizabeth (Box 12)
    - Doman, Bernard A. (Box 12)
    - Donations (Box 12)
    - Cumbarton Oaks (Box 12)
    - E (miscellaneous) (Box 12)
    - F (miscellaneous) (Box 12)
    - Form letters and appeals (Box 12)
    - Fort Wayne meeting (Box 12)
    - G (miscellaneous) (Box 12)
    - H (miscellaneous) (Box 12)
    - Haushalter, Walter M. (Box 12)
    - Hoffman, Clare E. (Box 12)
    - Holman, (Mrs.) Rufus C. (Box 12)
    - Hudson, Charles B. (Box 12)
    - Hull, Cordell (Box 12)
    - I (miscellaneous) (Box 12)
    - Indiana meetings (Box 12)
    - J (miscellaneous) (Box 12)
    - Jews (Box 12)
    - Jones, J. Edward (Box 13)
    - K (miscellaneous) (Box 13)
    - Kalamazoo - list of names (Box 13)
    - Kellems, Vivien (Box 13)
    - Kenny, Mrs. Mary E. (Box 13)
    - Kent, Tyler (Box 13)
    - Knowles, (Mrs.) Beatrice (Box 13)
    - L (miscellaneous) (Box 13)
    - Liebold, Ernest (Box 13)
    - Lincoln Electric Company (Cleveland) (Box 13)
    - Lohle, (Mrs.) Marie (Box 13)
    - Lohbeck, Don (Box 13)
    - M (miscellaneous) (Box 13)
    - Mc (miscellaneous) (Box 13)
    - Madden, Charles A. (Box 13)
    - Marion, L. L. (Box 13)
    - Meeting tickets and notices (Box 13)
    - Meetings to be scheduled (Box 13)
    - Memos (Box 13)
    - Milwaukee meeting (Box 13)
    - Minneapolis meeting (Box 13)
    - Minneapolis City Council (Box 13)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 13)
    - Monreal (Mrs.) Philip (Box 13)
      (United Mothers of America)
    - Montgomery Ward Controversy - telegrams and clippings (Box 13)
    - Mote, Carl H. (Box 13)
      (include issues of "America Preferred")
    - N (miscellaneous) (Box 13)
    - National Blue Star Mothers of America (Box 13)
      (formerly Crusading Mothers of Pennsylvania, Mrs. Catharine Brown, president)
    - National Economic Council (Box 13)
    - Negro homeland (Box 13)
    - Newspaper clippings re Smith (Box 13)
    - Nye, Gerald P. (Box 13)
    - O (miscellaneous) (Box 13)
    - Office of Price Administration - gasoline rationing (Box 13)
    - Olympia (Detroit) circular (Box 13)
    - Our Sunday Visitor (Box 13)
      (Catholic Weekly Newspaper)
    - P (miscellaneous) (Box 13)
    - "Pattern for Revolution" (Box 13)
      (circulated by the Friends of Democracy)
    - "Peace Now" Movement (Box 13)
    - Petition Heads (Box 13)
    - Philadelphia meeting (Box 13)
    - Pittsburgh meeting (Box 13)
    - Press releases (Box 13)
    - R (miscellaneous) (Box 13)
    - Reilly, Lawrence (Box 13)
      (Concordia Seminary)
    - Reports to Congressional Committees (Box 13)
    - Republican National Convention, June 26-28
      - General (Box 13)
      - Newspaper clippings (Box 13)
    - Reynolds, Robert, R. (Box 14)
    - Romer, Harry (Box 14)
    - Roosevelt, F. D., material about (Box 14)
    - S (miscellaneous) (Box 14)
    - St. Louis meeting, Feb. 17
      - General (Box 14)
      - Clippings (Box 14)
    - St. Louis Rally, Mar. 25 (Box 14)
    - St. Louis meetings (various dates) (Box 14)
    - St. Louis Post Dispatch article on Smith (Box 14)
    - Sedition Trial, April (Box 14)
    - Senate Bill 666 (Box 14)
      (Austin-Wadsworth Bill)
    - Shepler, Charles H. (Box 14)
    - Smith, Dean E. (Box 14)
    - Smith, Gerald, Jr. (Box 14)
    - Sokolsky, George (Box 14)
    - Songs (Box 14)
    - Southard, Earl (Box 14)
    - Springer, Harvey H. (Box 14)
    - Stadsklev, C. O. (Box 14)
    - Stanley, Mrs. David (Box 14)
    - Stoffel, Joseph (Box 14)
    - Subscription Drive Ideas (Box 14)
    - T (miscellaneous) (Box 14)
    - U (miscellaneous) (Box 14)
    - Under Cover (Box 14)
      (re investigation of author John Roy Carlson)
    - V (miscellaneous) (Box 14)
    - Veterans (Box 14)
    - W (miscellaneous) (Box 14)
    - Wheeler, Burton K. (Box 14)
    - Wheeler, Nathaniel Herbert (Box 14)
    - Winchell, Walter (Box 14)
    - Winrod, Gerald P. (Box 14)
    - Wirt, William A. (Box 14)
    - X-Z (miscellaneous) (Box 14)
  - 1945
    - A (miscellaneous) (Box 14)
    - Addresses and telephone numbers (Box 14)
    - America First Party
      - Appeals and form letters (Box 14)
      - Notices of meetings (Box 14)
      - Oakland County recount (Box 14)
    - American Civil Liberties Union (Box 14)
    - American Council of Christian Churches (Box 14)
    - Anonymous (Box 14)
    - Asman, Lorence (Box 14)
    - Atrocity stories (Box 14)
    - B (miscellaneous) (Box 14)
    - Baerman, Ralph (Box 15)
    - Bretton Woods Plan (Box 15)
    - Buffalo meetings (Box 15)
    - C (miscellaneous) (Box 15)
    - Chicago meeting (Box 15)
      (form letter and responses seeking support for proposed meeting)
    - Chicago meetings: largely lists of names (Box 15)
    - Chicago meeting March 15, 1945 (Box 15)
    - Correspondence (Box 15)
    - Newspaper clippings (Box 15)
    - Circulars (Box 15)
    - Cleveland meetings (Box 15)
    - Close, Upton (Box 15)
    - Correspondence (miscellaneous) (Box 15)
    - Cross and the Flag promotional material (Box 15)
    - D (miscellaneous) (Box 15)
    - Daugherty, J. M. (Box 15)
    - D[eland], Dr. (Box 15)
    - Denver meetings (Box 15)
    - Detroit Mayoralty Election clippings (Box 15)
    - Detroit meetings (Box 15)
    - Dilling, Elizabeth (Box 15)
    - Donations (Box 15)
    - Dumbarton Oaks (Box 15)
    - E (miscellaneous) (Box 15)
    - Embassy Press (Box 15)
    - F (miscellaneous) (Box 15)
    - F.B.I. (Box 15)
    - For the Record (Box 15)
    - Form letters and appeals (Box 15)
    - G (miscellaneous) (Box 15)
    - Goff, Kenneth (Box 15)
    - Groefsema, Elmer (Box 15)
    - H (miscellaneous) (Box 15)
    - "Ham 'n' Eggs" (Box 15)
      (Payroll Guarantee Association)
    - Haushalter, Walter (Box 15)
    - Hudson, Charles (Box 15)
    - Huston, T. R. (Box 15)
    - I (miscellaneous) (Box 15)
    - Indianapolis (Box 15)
    - J (miscellaneous) (Box 15)
    - Jewish Sentinel (Box 15)
    - Jews (collected material) (Box 15)
    - K (miscellaneous) (Box 15)
    - Kent, Tyler (Box 15)
    - King-Trendle (Box 15)
      (WXYZ-Walter Winchell law suit)
    - Kister, Frederick (Box 15)
    - L (miscellaneous) (Box 15)
    - Lohbeck, Don (Box 15)
    - Los Angeles meetings
      - Spring trip correspondence (Box 15)
      - Press releases June-July (Box 15)
      - Fall trip (general) (Box 15)
      - Fall trip correspondence (Box 15)
    - M (miscellaneous) (Box 16)
    - Mc (miscellaneous) (Box 16)
    - McClanahan, Meade (Box 16)
    - McDaniel, Donald J. (Box 16)
    - Maertz, Homer (Box 16)
    - Meeting notices and tickets (Box 16)
    - Memos, 3 folders (Box 16)
    - Memos, confidential (Box 16)
    - Minneapolis meeting (Box 16)
    - Miscellaneous (and uncertain dating) (Box 16)
    - Mote, Carl H. (Box 16)
    - N (miscellaneous) (Box 16)
    - National Blue Star Mothers of America (Box 16)
      (Mrs. Catharine Brown)
    - National Economic Council (Box 16)
    - National Emergency Committee (Box 16)
    - Nationalist Political Organization (Box 16)
    - Nationalist News Service (Box 16)
      (including The Letter)
    - Nationalist News Service newsletters (Box 16)
    - Newspaper clippings (Box 16)
    - O (miscellaneous) (Box 16)
    - P (miscellaneous) (Box 16)
    - Perkins, Jonathan (Box 16)
    - Phelps, G. Allison (Box 16)
    - Pittsburgh meetings (Box 16)
    - Postwar Recovery Commission (Box 16)
    - Press releases (Box 16)
    - R (miscellaneous) (Box 16)
    - Rankin, John E. (Box 16)
    - Reilly, Lawrence (Box 16)
    - Romer, Harry (Box 16)
    - S (miscellaneous) (Box 16)
    - St. George, Maximilian J. (Box 16)
    - St. Louis meeting (Box 16)
    - Salt Lake City meeting (Box 16)
    - San Francisco (Box 16)
      (UN Conference)
    - San Francisco press releases (Box 16)
    - Shepler, Charles (Box 16)
    - Smith, Gerry, Jr. (Box 16)
    - Smith family (Box 16)
    - Southard, Earl (Box 16)
    - Springer, Harvey (Box 16)
    - Stanley, Mrs. David (Box 16)
      (United Mothers)
    - State Department (Box 16)
    - Stoffel Joseph (Box 16)
      (Economics League)
    - Stokes, Jeremiah (Box 16)
    - T (miscellaneous) (Box 17)
    - Terminiello, Rev. Arthur W. (Box 17)
    - Topeka meeting (Box 17)
    - U (miscellaneous) (Box 17)
    - V (miscellaneous) (Box 17)
    - Vandenberg, Arthur H. (Box 17)
    - Veterans (Box 17)
    - Vose, George (Box 17)
    - W (miscellaneous) (Box 17)
    - Wheeler, Burton K. (Box 17)
    - Williams, Claude (Box 17)
    - X-Z (miscellaneous) (Box 17)
  - 1946
    - A (miscellaneous) (Box 17)
    - America First Party (Box 17)
      (contracts for meeting halls and related)
    - America First Party, 2 folders (Box 17)
      (record of checks and money orders received)
    - American Civil Liberties Union (Box 17)
    - Anderson, Charles, Jr. (Box 17)
    - Armstrong, George W. (Box 17)
    - Asman, Lorence (Box 17)
    - B (miscellaneous) (Box 17)
    - Baerman, Ralph (Box 17)
    - Ballagh, Blanche (Box 17)
    - Blake, Aldrich (Box 17)
    - Buffalo meetings (Box 17)
    - C (miscellaneous) (Box 17)
    - Celina (Ohio) meetings (Box 17)
    - Chase, Beatrice (Box 17)
    - Chicago meetings (Box 17)
    - Chicago Trial for Contempt, newspaper clippings (Box 17)
    - Christian Veterans of America (Box 17)
      (Frederick Kister, Director)
    - Cincinnati names (Box 17)
    - Cleveland meetings (Box 17)
    - Close, Upton (Box 17)
    - Committee on Un-American Activities (Box 17)
    - Congress on Civil Rights, Detroit, April 27-28 (Box 17)
    - Cross and the Flag (miscellaneous) (Box 17)
    - Cross and the Flag subscriptions, 2 folders (Box 17)
    - D (miscellaneous) (Box 17)
    - Dennis, Lawrence (Box 17)
    - Detroit meetings (Box 17)
    - Dilling, Albert (Box 18)
    - Dilling, Elizabeth (Box 18)
    - Doman memos (Box 18)
    - Donations, record of (Box 18)
    - E (miscellaneous) (Box 18)
    - Embassy Press (Box 18)
    - Emergency letters - fund raising (Box 18)
    - Essig, Edith (Box 18)
    - F (miscellaneous) (Box 18)
    - Federation of Americanization (Box 18)
    - Form letters and circulars (Box 18)
    - G (miscellaneous) (Box 18)
    - Goff, Kenneth (Box 18)
    - H (miscellaneous) (Box 18)
    - "Ham 'n' Eggs" (Box 18)
    - Haushalter, Walter (Box 18)
    - Hogg, James D. (Box 18)
    - I (miscellaneous) (Box 18)
    - J (miscellaneous) (Box 18)
    - Jaques, Norman (Box 18)
      (member, Canadian Parliament)
    - K (miscellaneous) (Box 18)
    - Kansas City meetings (Box 18)
    - L (miscellaneous) (Box 18)
    - Lohbeck, Don (Box 18)
    - Los Angeles meeting (Box 18)
    - Los Angeles meeting name cards (Box 18)
    - Lucas, Keith (Box 18)
    - M (miscellaneous) (Box 18)
    - Mc (miscellaneous) (Box 18)
    - McClanahan, Meade (Box 18)
    - Memos, interoffice, 2 folders (Box 18)
    - Midwestern Political Survey Institute (Box 18)
    - Midwestern Political Survey Institute donations (Box 18)
    - Minneapolis meeting (Box 18)
    - Mote, Carl H. (Box 18)
      (National Farmer's Guild)
    - N (miscellaneous) (Box 19)
    - National Blue Star Mothers of America (Box 19)
    - Newsletter (Box 19)
      (including The Letter
    - Newspaper clippings (Box 19)
    - O (miscellaneous) (Box 19)
    - Oakland, Calif. (Box 19)
    - P (miscellaneous) (Box 19)
    - Perkins, Rev. Jonathan E. (Box 19)
    - Pittsburgh meetings (Box 19)
    - Press releases (Box 19)
    - Prospective list of nationalists (Box 19)
    - R (miscellaneous) (Box 19)
    - Reports to Congress (Box 19)
    - Roosevelt circular (Box 19)
      (also some of background material)
    - S (miscellaneous) (Box 19)
    - St. George, Maximilian (Box 19)
    - St. Louis meeting: Nationalist Congress, May 28-29 (Box 19)
    - St. Louis meetings (Box 19)
    - Salt Lake City (Box 19)
    - San Francisco (Box 19)
    - Smith family: parents and son (Box 19)
    - Sorenson, Mrs. S. C. (Box 19)
    - Southard, Earl (Box 19)
    - Springer, Harvey (Box 19)
    - Stanley, Mrs. David (Box 19)
    - Stask, Al (Box 19)
    - Stoffel, Joseph (Box 19)
    - Stokes, Jeremiah (Box 19)
    - Swift, Wesley A. (Box 19)
    - T (miscellaneous) (Box 19)
    - Tenney Committee (Box 19)
    - Terminiello, Rev. A. W. (Box 19)
    - U-V (miscellaneous) (Box 19)
    - Viroqua (Wisc.) Centennial (and speech) (Box 19)
    - W (miscellaneous) (Box 19)
    - Winrod, Gerald P. (Box 20)
    - X-Z (miscellaneous) (Box 20)
  - 1947
    - A (miscellaneous) (Box 20)
    - Advertisements (Box 20)
    - America First Party record of checks and money orders received, 2 folders (Box 20)
    - American Anti-Communist Association (Box 20)
    - Armstrong, George W. (Box 20)
    - Asman, Lorence (Box 20)
    - B (miscellaneous) (Box 20)
    - Baerman, Ralph (Box 20)
    - Benge, Mrs. L. E. (Box 20)
    - Bilbo, Theodore (Box 20)
    - Boston meeting (Box 20)
    - Buffalo meeting (Box 20)
    - C (miscellaneous) (Box 20)
    - Christian Nationalist Crusade - list of checks and money orders received (Box 20)
    - Cleveland meeting (Box 20)
    - Commercial Publishers (Box 20)
    - Complaints (Box 20)
    - Correspondence (general) (Box 20)
    - Cross and the Flag
      - Communications with Post Office (Box 20)
      - Subscriptions (Box 20)
    - D (miscellaneous) (Box 20)
    - Davis, J. Boyd (Box 20)
    - Detroit meeting (Box 20)
    - Doman, Bernard (Box 20)
    - Douglas, Ga. (Box 20)
    - Douglas, Helen Gahagan (Box 20)
    - E (miscellaneous) (Box 20)
    - Elkhorn meeting (Box 20)
    - F (miscellaneous) (Box 20)
    - Federation of Americanization (Box 20)
    - Form letters and circulars (Box 20)
    - Fort Worth meeting (Box 20)
    - Friends of Democracy (Box 20)
    - G (miscellaneous) (Box 20)
    - Goff, Kenneth (Box 20)
    - H (miscellaneous) (Box 21)
    - Hamilton, John (Box 21)
    - Hill, Ed (Box 21)
    - I (miscellaneous) (Box 21)
    - Insignia and letterhead design (Box 21)
    - J (miscellaneous) (Box 21)
    - Jaques, Norman (Box 21)
    - Jones, Ellis O. (Box 21)
    - K (miscellaneous) (Box 21)
    - Kister, Frederick (Box 21)
      (Christian Veterans Political Counsel)
    - L (miscellaneous) (Box 21)
    - Latimer, J. Austin (Box 21)
    - Lohbeck, Donald A. (Box 21)
    - Long, George (Box 21)
    - M (miscellaneous) (Box 21)
    - Mc (miscellaneous) (Box 21)
    - McFarland, W. Henry (Box 21)
    - Mailing Lists (Box 21)
    - Manney, E. E. (Box 21)
    - Mannery Publishing Co. (Box 21)
    - Mathews, Jerry (Box 21)
    - Memos: interoffice, 5 folders (Box 21)
    - Midwestern Political Survey Institute donations (Box 21)
    - N (miscellaneous) (Box 21)
    - National Blue Star Mothers of America (Box 21)
    - National Committee (Box 21)
    - News letters (Box 22)
    - Newspaper clippings (Box 22)
    - Norris, J. Frank (Box 22)
    - O (miscellaneous) (Box 22)
    - Operatives (Box 22)
      (includes papers, 1943-1947)